<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Two Trees Olive Oil</string>
    <string name="description_text">
        Through each generation we’ve adapted and evolved, always keeping our sights set on creating
        the highest quality olive oil, while balancing our time-honored traditions with new
        innovative techniques.\n\n
        We’re passionate, even obsessive, about environmental sustainability,
        and we’re constantly looking to find ways to decrease our footprint on mother earth.\n\n
        We also share a strong sense of community with our customers, fellow farmers, and our beloved Santa
        Rosa neighbors who have embraced our business for many decades. Our high ethical standards
        and well-defined values are central to everything we do.
    </string>
    <string name="enter_label">Enter</string>
    <string name="home_label">Home</string>
    <string name="tours_label">Tours</string>
    <string name="shop_label">Shop</string>
    <string name="tours_header_label">TOURS</string>
    <string name="tours_content">Imagine your special event hosted against the sun-drenched
        backdrop of a 35-acre olive orchard in the beautiful rolling hills of Northern California.
        Wake up to songbirds flittering about the lush grounds of our 20-room bed and breakfast, and
        feast on mouth-watering breakfasts made from local, organic ingredients. We’re expert hosts
        who’ve thrown some monumental parties and hosted a wide range of events from anniversaries,
        to charity events, to weddings, and much more.
    </string>
    <string name="shop_header_label">Our products</string>
    <string name="shop_button_label">Continue Shopping</string>
    <string name="cart_content">Don’t forget about using the coupon codes you’ll
        find around our website. They change frequently, but are always a great bargain… if we
        do say so ourselves. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out. We love
        helping our customers.
    </string>
    <string name="bottle_image">Image of the olive oil bottle</string>
    <string name="product_size_label">%d ml bottle</string>
    <string name="product_image_label">Bottle of olive oil</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart_label">Add to Cart</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_granted">Storage permission granted!</string>
</resources>